[{"answer": "She tells me you haven't been sleeping well", "docId": "Gods-and-Monsters.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Then take the pills", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Quite", "docId": "Gods-and-Monsters.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What rumors might those be", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "\"Frankenstei", "docId": "Gods-and-Monsters.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Still.  You must be rich.  Making a couple of famous movies like those", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I apologize for going on like this. It's the Sunday painter in me.  Of course I can understand your refusal.  It's a great deal to ask of someone", "docId": "Gods-and-Monsters.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Indeed.  I'd pay for the privilege of drawing your head", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "These old movies are such a hoot. They thought they were being scary, but they're just funny", "docId": "Gods-and-Monsters.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Funny is funny and scary is scary. You don't mix them", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What's that mean", "docId": "Gods-and-Monsters.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I wasn't going to try anything", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "It means it's too cold to go swimming.  And I don't mean the water", "docId": "Gods-and-Monsters.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Yeah, and I'm never going to smoke another cigarette", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "It never crossed your mind", "docId": "Gods-and-Monsters.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "All the old men I know think about nothing but sex", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "In the sequel, my friend, two lady scientists should make a monster. And our monster would be my friend", "docId": "Gods-and-Monsters.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "More your line", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I would've thought Mr. my friend would be more your line", "docId": "Gods-and-Monsters.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "My line nowadays runs to Rin Tin Tin.  Dogs are so much more dependable than men", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Saw your movie the other night. Watched it with some friends", "docId": "Gods-and-Monsters.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I liked it.  We all did", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Did you now", "docId": "Gods-and-Monsters.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Did anyone laugh", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "The world is just one kis", "docId": "Gods-and-Monsters.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "my friend with a lawnmower", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "You're talking through your hat now", "docId": "Gods-and-Monsters.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "You were a soldier", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Not at all.  I was in the foxholes myself", "docId": "Gods-and-Monsters.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I was an officer", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "my friend.  The friend I thought was in that place", "docId": "Gods-and-Monsters.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Girl?  Oh.  my friend", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "You are much too human", "docId": "Gods-and-Monsters.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Don't move", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Oh my friend", "docId": "Gods-and-Monsters.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Nothing I didn't deserve", "qsentId": 36}]